hello my name is green and welcome back
to another episode of hermitcraft i am
starting today's episode in the shopping
district because i've got a few errands
to run the first is buying up all of the
dark prismarine for my base because i
saw that it was stocked and i think we
shouldn't be around the bush we should
just take the lot
wait can we afford the lot i i can't
afford the lot oh we got we gotta we
gotta dig deep here okay we're we're a
few diamonds short and also i've been
doing a little bit of prospecting and
now i did reserve this place for a shop
later on
but i actually noticed that some people
have been doing exactly the same
thing
look at this
someone has purchased this over here
this large square
and someone and i do know who this one
is this one is good times with scar and
i thought i'd take this opportunity who
he has clearly meticulously counted out
how many spaces he needs and i thought
i just uh i'd sneakily very very
sneakily
just uh pop in
and purchase one of these from right
under his nose
it's free real estate
and uh he can buy it back from me at a
later date or i could make
i could make a shop within his shop
later on i don't know if he's gonna
notice but i want that to be claimed as
as as very subtly as possible all we got
to do is pay for that bit now boom mine
so as long as he doesn't notice this
should be really really funny and the
same goes over here in fact i might
claim a couple of spots but i will
actually need to get some more diamonds
for that two diamonds
isn't quite going to cut it especially
as i need these for some shulker boxes
from scars new shop the chest monster
five diamonds for a shulker box oh all
other storage boxes are free with a
purchase
that is
wonderful there we go that's three
shulker boxes for me
and i guess i'm gonna take
did you hear
where did this
am i going mad there's there's no
skeleton right i'm losing my marbles i'm
losing my absolute mind
i heard i heard it
and now it's just what the heck what is
he with this server and weird flying
arrows if i re-log and it's gone
it's gone okay right um i was gonna take
through i was gonna take three
ender chests
what
it's back
is there someone here and i just didn't
know oh wait i think i figured it out i
think it must have come from hypno okay
i'm not losing my mind okay i've lost my
mind it's gone again now have i moved up
the leaderboard
yes that great that grain character is
gone and i am now in fourth place
i mean i still got a long way to go 170.
we could do this let's quickly head back
to the base and see what we can do we
are officially down to three diamonds
three
three diamonds that is rough that is
very rough and also i need to check if
this thing works now i have seen a
couple of iron golems and the fact that
there are no iron golems here is a good
sign because it means that they should
be going in there hello yes hello hello
let's take a look you know what it's
worked there was only three in there to
begin with then i spawned one and that's
another three meaning
there's probably been three more iron
golems and it is trickle i mean it was
it was a very small retro fit but it
seems to be working i also see that scar
has finished decorating the creeper farm
and i've got to say it is gorgeous oh
it's gorgeous i must admit this crystal
here though
doesn't it remind you of like the sims
it reminds me of the crystal that's like
above sims characters how about just
show version
that's my best sims impression
either way this looks absolutely amazing
good job scar and i can see that scar's
been working on something over here as
well he's cleared out a whole bunch of
space so this area is really starting to
become completely transformed
anyway i have been working on
dink hello ding ding ding ding ding
is it is it a message from mumbo
he or did he reply
shulker box
[Music]
oh a message but not from mumbo
not for a mom and 12 12 spruce doors
now if this blows up i'm gonna be really
mad
oh okay that is a really annoying sound
but it's the only way i'm gonna know if
mumbo's gonna message me what is this a
message but not from mumbo just some is
it a gift is it a gift of shulker boxes
i've been sending mumbo more and more
messages like
like a very needy girlfriend
hi mumbo hope you're okay i'm just it's
just gonna get progressively more more
annoying just yeah just keep just you
know he'll text back eventually it's
cool so in my down time i've been
working on something and it's to do with
my villager situation yes hello hello
hello now i have actually managed to
make this iron farm work i saw some eye
golem spawn but they were just standing
here looking down into it so a very very
simple change that we're going to do
is just a bit of water to push them in
and then it will it will literally be as
simple as that and it will work and it
should just push the golems ever so
slightly in there the problem is now of
course there's nowhere for the golems to
actually spawn i don't really know how
they work but the other thing that i
want to do i really want to improve this
i i'd never intended for this to be a
proper farm but it ended up being one
now i've enlisted the help of a pesky
bird here he is
what are you doing pesky bird now i want
to get these guys to turn into zombies
now i've never done this before so the
pesky bird hopefully when i when i push
him in here he should
go and infect all these guys now they've
already got trades that i really really
want to keep but i want them to be
cheaper than they currently are so
yeah i've never done this before so i'm
just going to go for it as you can see
i've already prepared golden apples and
splash weaknesses potions it should be
okay i just need to get these guys
uh all zombified hello right he's in go
on pesky bird
let's see how this goes oh no
the piskey bird is whiskey bird i might
need to power some more rails here
maybe i just need to let him loose but i
think he might he might kill some of my
villagers
hello oh let's just just do it
dude the pesky bird
the whiskey i think he's just gonna kill
them i don't think he's gonna infect
them how does this work
oh there we go yes yes pesky bird more
more we will we will cure them all hello
hello oh and look oh it's all going so
well
oh no
oh no no no no no no it's too bright
it's too bright it's too bright no
they're all dying they're all dying i
didn't think this through
oh no
we lost so many men
okay so that didn't go well
they were all panicking but we got some
we got some zombies here
all right let's get some of these guys
cured then
splash one of those
boom boom
that's dramatic
well this hasn't gone this hasn't gone
particularly well
i maybe should have put these guys in
minecarts they're still saying hello
oh i saved him i saved him
get out get out get out get out get out
okay so i got my mending guy
wow
come on totally worth it come on you can
do it you can do it
three
two i was so close
man we lost some good we lost some good
guys in this purge i think we're gonna
have to start putting these guys
in a proper villager system because this
this weird greenhouse cage it's not
working out for me it's not working out
for me at all we're gonna get these guys
all nice and stored up i was never
fussed about this before but we're gonna
do it so give me some time because we're
about to completely transform
what this villager base looks like this
was 100
a complete failure of an experiment
[Music]
i don't really know how to tell you all
this but i've been through probably the
worst minecraft experience i had
literally the worst day imaginable so as
you can see i've created my villager
breeder and the uh the zombie zone and
then it gets and then it splashes them
with weakness and it gives me good deals
and you can see i've got a few villagers
here and i've been steadily trading with
these guys
now the issue here is that this
doesn't look like a lot of work but it
actually took me all day
so many things went wrong
and i've never wanted to quit minecraft
more it just nothing wanted to work but
i'm out the other side now i have got it
set up i can trade with them and i've
got some really good deals and i've been
stocking up on some of the most
important stuff
golden carrots and you also noticed that
part of my infrastructure upgrades was
another farm that i've just hidden
inside this cave here because it's not
meant to be that important uh milan and
pumpkin farm which has been slowly going
away as well and that's gonna help me
get the emeralds and all this stuff my
goodness villagers
are
a pain and i tell you what i am shutting
up shop for today i am done with these
villagers they can all go to bed because
i i want nothing to do with them anymore
i have had enough some of the issues
that i had the villagers were escaping
they turned into zombies then they
burned in the sunlight then i've this is
like pesky bird number five he kept
getting out i couldn't find right
zombies that would take the items off me
enough of that enough of this closing up
shop i'll come back to this another day
to set it up because i would like to add
some more villagers i just don't think
my heart can take it it has been it's
been a rough day
really rough day but we are now with
fresh energy and it is done so i am
actually gonna send a bunch of 64 golden
carrots i'm not sure if mumbo's at the
stage where he's got loads of golden
carrots so i think he might appreciate
it so we'll send off some friendship
carrots hope he likes them
please text me back soon mambo
by the way i'm really i'm really not
bothered about it it's just it's just a
bit funny at this point i'm really not
upset i haven't actually had a chance to
keep building my base so i'm going to
save that for next episode i've been
stockpiling some resources today's been
a bit of a an admin inventory and
getting my infrastructure together it's
been an absolute nightmare and the next
thing that i need to do which is really
important i need to get myself a beacon
now i i told you i've been grinding away
i've been i've been getting all the
materials i even grinded out with the
skeletons so we're going to take this
we're going to go somewhere and we are
going to fight the wither i want to kind
of fight it in the open i've i've kind
of cheesed it in the past where i've
sort of hidden from it in a cave this
time i want to take it somewhere a
little bit more open let's set up a
respawn station in case i die and uh
because i don't want to lose all this
stuff now can you can you spawn in the
wither
this way like like this
that's some cursed minecraft right there
actually before i put in this last
wither head i think in order to defeat
the wither
i must become
someone who is better at fighting
someone who's basically not me
i must become
the hero the server never wanted i must
become
a wither fighting hero all right let's
do it see if i can fly in and do this
oh there it goes there it goes now we
just wait i probably don't want to be
too close to it you know what this might
actually be slightly easier
from a floor just just letting him fly
around because like he is his aim is
pretty bad
i think he's yet to hit me i can
probably just i can probably get him
from just flying by
this is easy
literally just passed through him and
hit i'm so used to flying and stuff he's
never going to hit me in the air he's
getting higher
we're both just like dancing in the air
are you going to come back
he's just getting higher
i've never seen a weather do this he
looks like a hot air balloon is he
coming back down
i have never seen a with a fight like
this
bruh
are you are you coming down i don't
think i i think he's stuck up there
all right right well i better get back
up there because
man
thank goodness i've got enough rockets
but
seriously i don't think he's coming down
it's probably the most epic with a fight
though all mid-air
the problem is of course
that the server is a little bit on the
laggy side so it's actually hard for me
to control everything
all right all right he's in his
mid-stage now
i've i've completely lost the floor how
high we're
650 blocks in the air i got a i got a
good few hits on in there
i'm currently a thousand blocks in the
air
one
should be the last one
i got him i got him i got him
where did the where did the star where's
the star
oh the xp is going down
here we go
wait there it is did i catch it
catch it catch it skydive
we made it now how bad would it be if it
landed in the lava
oh my goodness that would have been
awful i haven't caught it but i don't
know where it is either there it is
the netherstar
the netherstar and the wither head we
did it
we got the beacon that was the strangest
thing i've ever experienced it was
actually very close hey look just goes
to show you can accomplish anything when
you're a hero and i suppose
you want me to take off the mask do you
you wanna know you wanna know who i
really am fine i'll i'll take off the
mask boom pesky bird
there are there's many layers to this
superhero
but for now i think it's safe to say
that we saved the server from an
impending wither escape no idea where
that came from and now it is our duty as
the only superhero on this server to
save anyone who needs help
and of course it is our duty to make
sure that our neighbors are safe
where did he go
oh
another one
oh scar
when will you learn
oh there he is there he is he's just
frolicking around his newly planted
forest
i want to get his attention
did that hit him
where did that go
it's over scar
i have the high ground
we've got a really good amount of
minecraft heads mob heads um but i have
no idea what these are worth they're
probably not worth a lot so i want to
quickly visit
uh the the head game board and see
what's going on with what's worth what i
would really like to win this mini game
because i am dead broke i've got like
two diamonds to my name oh my
goodness
what is going on here
every time i come back here there's just
more and more signs it's turning into a
bit of an essay
all right let's have a little look the
bounty board will show special bonus
points tasks
five chill bee heads chill b i don't
know how you get those three different
colored sheep
uh 20 cod heads now that shouldn't be
too difficult
zuma jevin i think i want to opt out of
pvp i don't really want to go for pvp
kills anymore three different color
sheep now that one's quite an
interesting one and cod okay we're gonna
go for the cod heads and the colored
sheep one and there's now band heads no
more of these cave spiders no no no no
no i think someone might have submitted
a lot of cave spiders oh man we've moved
down to sixth place oh
how are we meant to compete you know i'd
really like to win this because like i
said pretty broke on the diamond front
but i don't think i'm gonna be able to
win this alone
maybe maybe i'll uh i'll message scar
and see if he's got any any spare heads
lying around oh cod heads here we go hey
we got it we got one we got one okay 19
more to go you see the thing is
cod heads look a little bit like me it
feels like i'm uh
i'm taking my brother's lives you know
what i mean
boop on the schnitt up on the schnitt
excuse me that
don't mind me i'm just uh
killing all the ocean life
one more 19 there's the last one
okay that took a little bit longer than
i
was expecting i mean you can tell by the
amount of fish that are still just
floating in the water here
and you can tell by the amount of cooked
fish that i've got in my inventory
okay we got what we came for let's clean
this bounty
not sure it was worth it there's got to
be a better way of doing this
20 cod heads 75 points
20 cod heads 70 75 points green woo okay
so she knows she knows who it's from
bounty box
submitted okay that's another that's
another 75 points that sh might just
pump me up to i think that yeah that's
that's going to bring me pretty close
but
man
709 points that's uh
that's a long way to go you know what
i'm gonna message scar see if uh see
what he's got
scar where you at
oh scar you're not afk are you i'm
afraid afk is illegal sir
if he's afk
what can we do what can we do
part of me wants to take his head for
the
for the head hunt uh but the other half
of me just wants to see if he he comes
back in
well to be honest he should have heard
me if i was breaking this he should have
heard me
no nothing he's gone he's he's out i
think i think this superhero i'm here to
protect the server from afk is
i'm afraid that's illegal scar i know i
don't really want him to die how has he
got himself stuck in a bunch of leaves
scar
yes are you back are you okay can a man
just sleep in a tree amongst the leaves
i don't know what was going on there was
there was someone around here he was
just uh messing with you i don't know
why i scared them off don't worry
was it nemo because i have nemo in my
inventory now
yeah oh i got a i got a whole school of
fish
where'd you get off where did you get on
okay so i've been collecting uh cod
heads for the head game and i wanted to
ask you
if you had any extra heads and if you
wanted to go like halfsies into the game
because i'm so far behind on the points
and there's no way i can catch her i
can't i can catch up without a bit of
help you are nodding vigorously have you
got have you got something up your
sleeve i did and i was excited i run
over to the head game there's spiders
over there no problem i'm not scared of
spiders i find out that people are like
400 points ahead and i'm just like ah
because i thought i was going to be big
the big guy in town with 200 and
something points worth of dragon heads
but no
that wasn't even half of what cub and
crowless were so you didn't sit and they
left
you didn't you got them
how many how many go how many
dragon heads i've got 26 now 26 dragon
heads yeah they're worth 10 points they
all worth 10 points well okay so i'm i'm
roughly on about 250 points now if you
if you want to go harvesting with half
these with me i can submit them all and
then we can try and like bump our way up
the the leaderboard oh we can do that
like team up yep as far as i'm aware i
don't think there's anything wrong with
it we can go split split the diamonds
there is no authority there is no that
is
there is none that shopping districts
are free-for-all um
i didn't even pay for my shop and i was
making diamonds i eventually paid you
know i'm an honorable person but um
i even have like 30 uh shulker heads
that's 30 points right there i'm well up
for this but i also have like a long
term plan to win this head hunt i really
want to win as you can tell i'm
investing a lot of time into this
um i got a plan but the thing is
i don't trust the audience and they're
everywhere
they're everywhere they're in they're in
the jungle they're looking at me right
now and i i don't i don't trust them so
i'm a whisper whisper in your ear the
plan privately mm-hmm yeah okay yeah get
close
i okay the cape the game's my favorite
part
that's right i gotta keep my long-term
plan a secret from everyone don't worry
it will all come to pass but i don't
know how long the head hunt's going on
for so i've got to make sure
that i don't reveal my plan too early
because if i do that
then other people might do the same i
need to wait till the end but with scar
on board
this will be very interesting very
interesting indeed but i'm afraid that
is all we have time for today we got
actually quite a lot done i've had the
most frustrating episode of my life that
you didn't actually see trying to make
this thing worthwhile i don't even want
to look at that anymore i made a melon
and pumpkin farm and i defeated a wither
time to craft this into a beacon but
most importantly
i revealed to you my secret identities
that's right remember
there's two
okay i will see you in the next episode
good bye